A Guide to the Records of William James McKeefery, Vice President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1969-1973
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Student Personnel Division, Dr. James Dean. (Box-folder 22-923)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 22-924)
- James W. Dean, Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 22-925)
- Students, Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 22-926)
- Student Personnel Division J. Gordon Brown, Dean Student. (Box-folder 22-927)
- Student Personnel Division David E. Hill, Dean of Students. (Box-folder 22-928)
- Student Publications Board. (Box-folder 23-929)
- Students Fall Quarter. (Box-folder 23-930)
- Students Spring and Summer. (Box-folder 23-931)
- Students. (Box-folder 23-932)
- Appeals - Students. (Box-folder 23-933)
- Ronald Rollins. (Box-folder 23-934)
- Ernie Wilson. (Box-folder 23-935)
- Craig Brauman. (Box-folder 23-936)
- Steven Angle. (Box-folder 23-937)
- Gleason, Jane Patricia. (Box-folder 23-938)
- Robert Levin. (Box-folder 23-939)
- Dr. W.E. Lavery. (Box-folder 23-940)
- Thompson, Timothy. (Box-folder 23-941)
- Anthony Lester. (Box-folder 23-942)
- Dudley, Justin Dana. (Box-folder 23-943)
- Melancon, James M. (Box-folder 23-944)
- Tomkinson, Robert. (Box-folder 23-945)
- Wellington, Carol J. (Box-folder 23-946)
- Lazio, Deborah J. (Box-folder 23-947)
- Townsend, Richard D. (Box-folder 23-948)
- Houlihan, Peter M. (Box-folder 23-949)
- Samford, Mary S. (Box-folder 23-950)
- Hook - Williams Cadets. (Box-folder 23-951)
- Wayne Lottinville. (Box-folder 23-952)
- Fletcher, Charles. (Box-folder 23-953)
- Heffernan, James D. (Box-folder 23-954)
- Academic Affairs - L.F. Malpass - VP. (Box-folder 23-955)
- Academic Affairs - Donald C. Darnton. (Box-folder 23-956)
- Academic Affairs - Alfred H. Krebs. (Box-folder 23-957)
- Accounting Office accounts computer reports. (Box-folder 23-958)
- Administration - Stuart K. Cassell. (Box-folder 23-959)
- Administrative Intern Program. (Box-folder 23-960)
- Administrators. (Box-folder 23-961)
- Administration Conf. (Box-folder 23-962)
- Administration Conf. - Spring 1973. (Box-folder 23-963)
- Administration Conf. - Sept. 1972. (Box-folder 23-964)
- Admissions Office. (Box-folder 23-965)
- Affirmative Action. (Box-folder 23-966)
- Alumni Association. (Box-folder 23-967)
- American Association for Higher Education. (Box-folder 23-968)
- American Council on Education. (Box-folder 23-969)
- American Association University Administration. (Box-folder 23-970)
- American Council on Education Publications. (Box-folder 23-971)
- American Association University Professors. (Box-folder 23-972)
- Articulation. (Box-folder 23-973)
- Articulation Conf. (Box-folder 23-974)
- Athletic Association. (Box-folder 23-975)
- Associated Clubs. (Box-folder 23-976)
- Association of Virginia Colleges. (Box-folder 23-977)
- Athletics. (Box-folder 23-978)
- Atomic Energy Commission. (Box-folder 23-978a)
- Blacksuburg, Town of. (Box-folder 23-979)
- Board of Visitors. (Box-folder 23-980)
- Budget. (Box-folder 23-981)
- Building Committee. (Box-folder 23-982)
- Capital Outlay. (Box-folder 23-983)
- Career Counseling. (Box-folder 23-984)
- Class - Indep. Study. (Box-folder 23-985)
- Commencement Committee. (Box-folder 23-986)
- Computer Committee. (Box-folder 23-987)
- Commission on Student Affairs. (Box-folder 23-988)
- Community Colleges. (Box-folder 23-989)
- Computing Center. (Box-folder 23-991)
- Computing Center Log. (Box-folder 23-992)
- Consultants. (Box-folder 23-993)
- Consulting, Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 23-994)
- Consulting, Aug. - Oct. (Box-folder 23-995)
- Consulting, Oct. - Feb. (Box-folder 23-996)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 24-997)
- Cont. Education Center, Donaldson Brown. (Box-folder 24-998)
- Coop. Education. (Box-folder 24-999)
- Corps of Cadets. (Box-folder 24-1000)
- Counseling Center. (Box-folder 24-1001)
- Credit Union. (Box-folder 24-1002)
- Deans. (Box-folder 24-1003)
- Comm. Agency. (Box-folder 24-1004)
- Develop. University. (Box-folder 24-1005)
- EDUCOM. (Box-folder 24-1006)
- Enrollment. (Box-folder 24-1007)
- Excellence in Teaching. (Box-folder 24-1008)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 24-1009)
- H-1 Applications. (Box-folder 24-1010)
- Exchange of Visitors. (Box-folder 24-1011)
- International Programs. (Box-folder 24-1012)
- Judicial Committee. (Box-folder 24-1013)
- Jury Duty. (Box-folder 24-1014)
- Library. (Box-folder 24-1015)
- Learning Resources Center. (Box-folder 24-1016)
- Mayhew, Lewis B. (Box-folder 24-1017)
- Past. (Box-folder 24-1018)
- Mission Statement Of the University. (Box-folder 24-1019)
- Music. (Box-folder 24-1020)
- National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC). (Box-folder 24-1021)
- National Science Foundation. (Box-folder 24-1022)
- New Degree Programs. (Box-folder 24-1023)
- Patents. (Box-folder 24-1024)
- Peer Institutions. (Box-folder 24-1025)
- Personnel. (Box-folder 24-1026)
- Phi Delta Kappa. (Box-folder 24-1027)
- Philippines. (Box-folder 24-1028)
- Placement. (Box-folder 24-1029)
- Promotions. (Box-folder 24-1030)
- Purchasing. (Box-folder 24-1031)
- Recommendations, letters of. (Box-folder 24-1032)
- Research Division. (Box-folder 24-1033)
- Religious Affairs. (Box-folder 24-1034)
- Reston. (Box-folder 24-1035)
- Ryland, Walter H. (Box-folder 24-1036)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 24-1037)
- Salary. (Box-folder 24-1038)
- Scholarships, Student Aid. (Box-folder 24-1039)
- Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities. (Box-folder 24-1040)
- Southern Regional Educational Board. (Box-folder 24-1041)
- Space. (Box-folder 24-1042)
- Special Projects. (Box-folder 24-1043)
- Squires Student Center. (Box-folder 24-1044)
- Staff Meeting. (Box-folder 24-1045)
- Staff Meeting. (Box-folder 24-1046)
- Staff Meeting Minutes. (Box-folder 24-1047)
- State Council on Higher Education. (Box-folder 24-1048)
- Statements, January - June. (Box-folder 24-1049)
- Student Constitutional Affairs Board. (Box-folder 24-1050)
- Student Government Association. (Box-folder 24-1051)
- Student Personnel Division - James W. Dean, VP. (Box-folder 25-1052)
- Student Personnel Division - J. Gordon Brown, Student Services. (Box-folder 25-1053)
- Student Personnel Division - David E. Hill, Dean, Student Programs. (Box-folder 25-1054)
- Fraternity/Sorority Program. (Box-folder 25-1055)
- Student Health Service. (Box-folder 25-1056)
- Residence Hall Federation. (Box-folder 25-1057)
- Student Life Policies. (Box-folder 25-1058)
- Student Appeals Centennial Four. (Box-folder 25-1059)
- Students. (Box-folder 25-1060)
- Students - Appeals and Hearings. (Box-folder 25-1061)
- Scott Erb / William Suqrue. (Box-folder 25-1062)
- Mark Ganada. (Box-folder 25-1063)
- Steven C. Macht / Robert K. Rowe. (Box-folder 25-1064)
- Richard H. Wood. (Box-folder 25-1065)
- Telephone. (Box-folder 25-1066)
- Telecommunications. (Box-folder 25-1067)
- Traffic Appeals Subcommittee. (Box-folder 25-1068)
- Travel. (Box-folder 25-1069)
- Media. (Box-folder 25-1070)
- Paul Carter. (Box-folder 25-1071)
- Diane L. Steed. (Box-folder 25-1072)
- Diane M. Berg. (Box-folder 25-1073)
- Carl A. Greiilo. (Box-folder 25-1074)
- Study Abroad Programs. (Box-folder 25-1075)
- Task Forces. (Box-folder 25-1076\)
- Telephone. (Box-folder 25-1077)
- Traffic Appeals and Subcommittee. (Box-folder 25-1078)
- Traffic Comm. (Box-folder 25-1079)
- University Council - Current. (Box-folder 25-1080)
- University Council. (Box-folder 25-1081)
- Committee for Constitutional Revision. (Box-folder 25-1082)
- Finance - W.E. Lavery, VP. (Box-folder 25-1083)
- Files. (Box-folder 25-1084)
- Freedom of Information. (Box-folder 25-1085)
- Foreign Students - J. Malone, Advisor. (Box-folder 25-1086)
- Governor's Office. (Box-folder 25-1087)
- Honor Court. (Box-folder 25-1088)
- Housing - Campus. (Box-folder 25-1089)
- Information Services. (Box-folder 25-1090)
- Innovations, Task Force On. (Box-folder 25-1091)
- Faculty Senate. (Box-folder 25-1092)
- Institutional Research - O.I.R. General Correspondence. (Box-folder 25-1093)
- Institutional Research - O.I.R. Reports. (Box-folder 25-1094)
- Agenda - University Council Meeting. (Box-folder 25-1095)
- WJM - 1973 University Council: Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 25-1096)
- WJM - 1973 University Council: Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 25-1097)
- WJM - 1973 Committee to Study Revision of University Council. (Box-folder 25-1098)
- Minutes - University Council Meeting. (Box-folder 25-1099)
- WJM - 1973 University Center In Virginia. (Box-folder 25-1100)
- University Research Association: Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 25-1101)
- University Research Association: Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 25-1102)
- Visiting Scholars. (Box-folder 25-1103)
- Water Resources Research Center. (Box-folder 26-1104)
- Yeager, Jack - Administrative Intern. (Box-folder 26-1105)
- TMH - Returned Correspondence, January - June 1973. (Box-folder 26-1106)
- TMH - May 1973. (Box-folder 26-1107)
- TMH - April 1973. (Box-folder 26-1108)
- TMH - March. (Box-folder 26-1109)
- TMH - February. (Box-folder 26-1110)
- TMH - January. (Box-folder 26-1111)
- Agriculture, College of - James E. Martin, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1112)
- Agriculture, Departments - Correspondence. (Box-folder 26-1113)
- Architecture, Departments - Correspondence. (Box-folder 26-1114)
- Architecture, College of - Charles Burchard, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1115)
- Arts & Sciences, College of - William C. Havard, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1116)
- Arts and Sciences, Departments - Correspondence. (Box-folder 26-1117)
- Proposed Physics Branch Library. (Box-folder 26-1118)
- Computer Science Department. (Box-folder 26-1119)
- Physics - Nuclear Engineering. (Box-folder 26-1120)
- Business, College of - H. H. Mitchell, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1121)
- Business, Departments - Correspondence. (Box-folder 26-1122)
- Education, College of - Karl T. Hereford, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1123)
- Federal City College. (Box-folder 26-1124)
- Education Task Force. (Box-folder 26-1125)
- Education Task Force. (Box-folder 26-1126)
- Engineering, College of - Paul E. Torgersen, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1127)
- Land-Grant. (Box-folder 26-1128)
- Visualing Proposal. (Box-folder 26-1129)
- Callahan, J.D.; Bushwell, David; Prof. Dr. Cobb. (Box-folder 26-1130)
- Physical Plant Planning. (Box-folder 26-1131)
- Computing Center User's Guide - Vol. One. (Box-folder 26-1132)
- Extension Offerings and Enrollment. (Box-folder 26-1133)
- Campus Law Enforcement. (Box-folder 26-1134)
- Engineering, Departments - Correspondence. (Box-folder 26-1135)
- Home Economics, Departments - Correspondence. (Box-folder 26-1136)
- Extension Division - William E. Skelton, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1137)
- Graduate School - Fred W. Bull, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1138)
- Versatile Nuclear Reactor - Part One. (Box-folder 26-1139)
- Versatile Nuclear Reactor - Part Two. (Box-folder 26-1140)
- Universities Research Associates: Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 26-1141)
- Universities Research Associates: Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 26-1142)
- University Research Association. (Box-folder 26-1143)
- Atomic Energy Commission. (Box-folder 26-1144)
- University Sanctioned Awards Committee. (Box-folder 26-1145)
- Vinocour, S.M. Dr. (Joe). (Box-folder 26-1146)
- Visiting Scholars. (Box-folder 26-1147)
- Water Resources Research Center. (Box-folder 26-1148)
- Westinghouse. (Box-folder 26-1149)
- Wilfong, Rich (doctoral candidate). (Box-folder 26-1150)
- Women's Interdormitory Council. (Box-folder 26-1151)
- Jack Yeager. (Box-folder 26-1152)
- YWCA, YMCA. (Box-folder 26-1153)
- Agriculture & Life Sciences - James E. Martin, Dean. (Box-folder 26-1154)
- Agricultural Economics - J. Edwin Faris, Head. (Box-folder 26-1155)
- Agronomy, T.B. Hutcheson, Jr., Head. (Box-folder 27-1156)
- Anaerobic Bacteriology Lab: W.E.C. Moore. (Box-folder 27-1157)
- Animal Science - Milton B. Wise, Head. (Box-folder 27-1158)
- Biochemistry & Nutrition: Bruce M. Anderson, Head. (Box-folder 27-1159)
- Dairy Science: Raymond G.Cragle, Head. (Box-folder 27-1160)
- Entomology: J.M. Grayson, Head. (Box-folder 27-1161)
- Food Science & Technology: R.B. Lechowich, Head. (Box-folder 27-1162)
- Forestry & Wilidlife Science: J.F. Hosner, Director. (Box-folder 27-1163)
- Horticulture: Max E. Austin, Acting Head. (Box-folder 27-1164)
- Plant Pathology & Physiology: H.B. Couch, Head. (Box-folder 27-1165)
- Veterinary Science: D.F. Watson, Head. (Box-folder 27-1166)
- Architecture, College of: Charles Burchard, Dean. (Box-folder 27-1167)
- Building Construction. (Box-folder 27-1168)
- Center for the Study of New Communities, Reston, VA. (Box-folder 27-1169)
- Arts & Sciences, College of: William C. Harvard, Dean. (Box-folder 27-1170)
- Biology: Robert A. Paterson, Head. (Box-folder 27-1171)
- Chemistry: A.F. Clifford, Head. (Box-folder 27-1172)
- Computer Science. (Box-folder 27-1173)
- English - Wilson Snipes, Head. (Box-folder 27-1174)
- Geological Sciences: Gordon C. Grender, Head. (Box-folder 27-1175)
- History. (Box-folder 27-1176)
- Mathematics: C. Wayne Patty, Head. (Box-folder 27-1177)
- Performing Arts & Comm.: P.A. Distler, Head. (Box-folder 27-1178)
- Philosophy & Religion: N.L. Groover, Head. (Box-folder 27-1179)
- Physics: J.A. Jacobs, Head - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 27-1180)
- Physics: J.A. Jacobs, Head - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 27-1181)
- Political Science: James F. Herndon, Head. (Box-folder 27-1182)
- Sociology. (Box-folder 27-1183)
- Statistics. (Box-folder 27-1184)
- Business, College of: H.H. Mitchell, Dean. (Box-folder 27-1185)
- Accounting: R.J. Pattern, Head. (Box-folder 27-1186)
- Business Administration: R.L. King, Head. (Box-folder 27-1187)
- Economics: A. Pepelasis, Acting Head. (Box-folder 27-1188)
- Education, College of: Karl T. Hereford, Dean. (Box-folder 27-1189)
- Curriculum & Instruction: W.M. Worner, Head. (Box-folder 27-1190)
- Administration & Educ. Serv. (Box-folder 27-1191)
- Vocational - Technical Education. (Box-folder 27-1192)
- Health, Physical Education & Recreation: W.E. McCubbin. (Box-folder 27-1193)
- Engineering, College of: Paul E. Torgersen, Dean. (Box-folder 27-1194)
- Aerospace Engineering: J.A. Schertz, Head. (Box-folder 27-1195)
- Civil Engineering: R.D. Walker, Head. (Box-folder 27-1196)
- Electrical Engineering: W.A. Blackwell, Head. (Box-folder 27-1197)
- Engineering Mechanics: D. Frederick, Head. (Box-folder 27-1198)
- Industrial Engineering & Operations Research: M.H. Agee. (Box-folder 27-1199)
- Mechanical Engineering: J.B. Jones, Head. (Box-folder 27-1200)
- Minerals Engineering: J. Richard Lucas, Head. (Box-folder 27-1201)